wowmails.com 2009-05-18

# Privacy Policy

| Privacy Policy  
---  
**About this Privacy Policy**  
Who do they apply to  
Are these privacy policies likely to change  
Privacy Policy Statement  
How does administration use the information you provide?  
What about security?  
Why does this website record IP Addresses?  
What are cookies and why does this website use them?  
DoubleClick DART cookies  
What about other Websites?  
What is spam and does administration send it?  

About this Privacy Policy  
---  
**Who do they apply to**  
Everyone, nobody is excused from them, and it is the users responsibilty to keep up to date with changes to the privacy policy.  
Back to top  
**Are these privacy policies likely to change**  
Yes, the privacy policy may be changed as a requirement of Federal and/or State Laws.  
Back to top  
**Privacy Policy Statement**  
The administrator understands that you are concerned about your privacy. Thats why administration has created this privacy policy statement, to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.  
Back to top  
**How does administration use the information you provide?**  
Administration uses the information you provide to target and personalise the emails we send to you and the offers we make available to you. We do this to ensure that you only receive relevant and appropriate information. administration will not sell or give away your personal information to any other person, company or organisation, unless, it is required by law, or you expressly agree to us giving out your information. Demographic and profile data is only shared with administration affilliates and advertisers on an aggregate or collective basis. However, we will never tell our affilliates your name, your postal address or your email address and other such information.  
Back to top  
**What about security?**  
Administration has modern and robust security measures in place to protect the information you give to us from loss, misuse and alteration. We are constantly reviewing and upgrading these security measures to ensure the very best of protection to you.  
Back to top  
**Why does this website record IP Addresses?**  
When a user joins this website, our computers may record their IP address. In the event that we detect fraud or abuse of our program on our Web site and computers, we may use the IP address of the offender to take action against them. Ultimately this ensures greater protection for you and your personal information.  
Back to top  
**What are cookies and why does this website use them?**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on Wowmails.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts..  
Back to top  
**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx  
Back to top  
**What about other Websites?**  
This website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read the privacy statements of other websites that you use. This privacy statement applies only to websites owned and operated by the adminstrator of this site.  
Back to top  
**What is spam and does administration send it?**  
The widely accepted definition of SPAM is unsolicited commercial email, or in other words, email of a commercial nature that the recipient does not want. administration does not send SPAM. If you have received unwanted email sent from administration, or purporting to be sent from administration, please contact admin[at]wowmails.com. If you have any questions about the privacy and permission practices of the administration website or your dealings with administration, please contact admin[at]wowmails.com. We are committed to being of service to you and resolving any issues that may arise.  
Back to top
